Musa Abukhalaf

San Diego, CA, • M.(279)202-4823 • http://www.mv-labs.com • musawork@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

Top-professional **DESIGNER** who is seeking a full-time position at a distinguished reputability company, where I can improve my interpersonal skills and exchange experiences.

Executive summary

Experience in taking a project from idea to implementation throughout 2D and 3D design processes. Unique skills in 3D visualization • product styling • prototyping • 3D printing • product developments • digital printing. Backed up with a unique academic field.

EDUCATION:

MA in 3D Computer Animation: Bournemouth University, United Kingdom.

Bachelor in Graphic Design Applied Science University, Jordan.

Diploma in Automobile & internal Combustion Engine, Amman Engineering College (Polytechnic).

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE:

April 2016 - May 2021

Print It Fast

Product and Development Director

- Implementing products development aligned with R&D for new and existing products for products enhancements. Developed the UX for the products.
- Managing the 2D and 3D design and Prototyping, 3D printing, digital fabrication, departments, and productions. With a result of increasing the sales by 70%.

August 2008 - Feb. 2016

Industrial Professor

German-Jordanian University - Jordan

- Created, and Developed several department programs. Included Packaging, Photography, Product Design, 3D and 2D Animation, UX&UI, and Prototyping. All the programs are 80% practical linked to real clients. Increased the hiring rate after graduation from 65% to 90%.
- Established a new digital lab with state-of-the-art equipment including capability in 3D printing.
- T.O.T Program as a guest industrial professor at Magdeburg University (3D printing, clay modelling, Product design, prototyping).

June 2005 - June 2008

Art Director

DigitalPro, San Diego, CA

- Supervised the staff and created a new visual look and feature designs layouts, covers, packaging, brochures, and new advertisements, in a fast-paced and demanding environment.
- Supported the art team by handling their needs throughout creating designs, illustrations, and photography.
 Managed and handled several important projects that needed high technical skills and deep knowledge in Graphic designing & pre-press. All projects were delivered prior to the deadline and exceeding the expected quality.

Sept. 2002 - Feb. 2005

Full-time Lecturer

Amman University, Jordan

- Developed and implemented new methods of teaching to reflect the latest market trends.
- Took the initiative to develop the digital arts, multimedia, and rapid prototyping program.

AWARDS:

NHS, LEEDS, 2nd place poster design for Radiology, United Kingdom.

STYLE UP YOUR GOLF COMPETITION, Winner, 1st place, Jordan.

VOLVO, 2nd Place International Award Print and Website Design Project, USA.

TRAINING/ WORKSHOPS / CERTIFICATES/ GENERAL ASSIGNMENTS:

- Jury member, mentor for several incubators/accelerators as manufacturing and technical expert.
- Magdeburg University Germany: Design and build 3D printer PLA Pellets

CERTIFICATE:

Adobe Suite: Photoshop / In Design / Illustrator / After Effects.

Maxon: Cinema 4D.

Design Foundations: Prototyping and Manufacturing

Renewable Energy: Solar system (design, build & assembly, on grid off grid systems, troubleshooting)

3D Mock-up Creation with Cinema 4D Introduction to Ecological Packaging

Sustainable Packaging Design for E-commerce

SOFTWARE AND HARDWARE TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- 3D Printers: Zcorp powder molding, Form2, Ultimaker, Zortrax, Lulzbot, Envisiontech, Delta Wasp 3MT.
 3D Scanner Zcorp 800
- Hands-on Experience in MAC, PC,
- Pre-Press Operation: Layout, Imposition for Offset and Digital printing.
- Mind Mapping, Creative thinking, Reverse engineering, MVP.

PERSONAL SKILLS:

- Excellent leadership
- Management skill
- Problem solving skills
- Outstanding customer service
- Extraordinary communication skills
- · Impressive organizational abilities